Charlie Bradbury
Charlie Bradbury.
Charlie
Charlie.
小孩儿们 最近好吗
What's up, bitches.
一个高中辍学生
How does a high school dropout become.
是怎么变成罗曼公司最聪明的员工的
One of the brightest minds at Roman Inc.
根据以前的情况 我
Historically, I have had this.
不怎么尊重当权
Problem with authority.
有没有一种怪物吸附体一类的东西
Is there such a thing as monster magnet.
你什么时候变得这么专业的
When did you become such an expert.
自从你们离开
After you guys left.
我就开始找各种各样的怪物
I dug into all things monstrous.
我有点着迷了
I'm a wee bit obessesive.
如果这次是这么个用法
If a wee bit, completely.
我说
There's a.
读猎魔 和真正猎魔
Big difference between reading about hunting.
完全不一样
And actually hunting.
我其实
I'm…I'm more.
我就是个初学者
Hunter-in-training.
不值得你动手
Totally not worth killing.
你真的应该
You know you really should come back.
跟我去基地
And dig through our archives.
你绝对是女学者
You are definitely a woman of letters.
我喜欢这个名字
I like the sound of that.
那是全地球最安全的地方
It just the safest place on earth.
能隔离一切邪恶生物
Warded against any evil ever created.
具有有关超自然的丰富宝库
It is the supernatural mother lode.
如果知识就是力量的话
If knowledge is power.
那这就是地球上最强大的地方
This is the most powerful place on earth.
Sam 我们找到栖息地了
Sam, I think we found the bat cave.
对接完成
Protocol's complete.
我叫James
James.
- James Haggerty - Peter Jenkins
- James Haggerty - Peter Jenkins.
我们做的都对吗
Did we do everything right.
不是应该
Shouldn't.
建这个垃圾堆居然花了三年时间
Took three years to build this dump.
垃圾堆
Dump.
垃圾堆吗
你开什么玩笑
Are you kidding.
你知道我们在哪儿吗 这儿
You realize where we are.This.
在这乌七八糟的世界里
This dump is the last true beacon of light.
这地方是光明的基地
In world gone topsy-turvy.
这个垃圾堆
This dump.
是正义与邪恶斗争的中心
Is the epicentre of the ultimate chess match between good and evil.
（六个月后）
真是垃圾堆一个
What a dump.
知道我想到什么了吗 这次的任务 我本来以为是
You know what I got?This assignment I thought they'd be.
我也说不清 应该很兴奋
I don't know…Excitement.
是次刺激的冒险
Adventure.
冒险不是什么好事 孩子
There's nothing worse an adventure my boy.
相信我
Trust me.
外线765
Extention 765.
是的
Yes.
不是
No.
那不是密码
That's not the password.
这里是有协议的
It's protocol here, young lady.
我们会等
We'll be waiting.
来了一位客人 是个猎人
Have a guest, damn hunter.
Frank家的
Frank's kid.
真的吗 哇哦
Really?Whoa.
他对她所作的一切 真是太厉害了
What he did for her?That was really something.
他确实很厉害
He was something all right.
我天 真的是你啊
Holy bucket, it's really you.
是的 真的是我 新手
That's right, rookie, it's really me.
我是Dorothy
Dorothy.
请问
Now.
你们两位谁愿意帮我
Which one of you genuises is gonna help.
杀了西方坏女巫
Me to kill the wicked witch.
（如今）
嗨 大麋鹿
Hello, moose.
你们要更多恶魔名字
You want more demon names.
我想要一间观景房
I wanna a room with a view.
我们可以讨论啊
We can discuss this.
让我伸个腿也行啊
I'd settle for streching my legs.
可恶
Ballocks.
嘿
Hey.
Kevin还好吗
How'd it go with Kevin.
那个小书呆子
That little nerd is in a.
在Branson一个温馨的小旅馆里
Lovely warm motel room in Branson.
他有48小时可以看付费黄片
He's got about 48 hours of pay-per-porn.
还有Kenny Rogers的歌
And Kenny Rogers ahead of him.
- 他什么感受 - 嗯
- How's he feeling? - Well.
他盯着天使预言板
He stared the angle tablet.
一路上一直念着falafe
Repeated the word 'falafe' being the entire ride.
孩子累坏了
Kid cracked.
希望小休假能让他 清醒清醒
Hope he's break will…clear his head.
在发生了那么多以后 我想
You know after eveything that happened I think.
我们也能休个假什么的
We can use a little breaker ourselves.So.
我帮你买了权力游戏第一季
I pick you up season 1 Game of Thrones.
然后再叫个外卖
Think we can get a little of take out.
好吧 先说 我觉得我找到帮Cass的方法了
All right, well first, I think might to find a way yo help Cass.
你跟他聊过了吗
Did you talk to him.
没有
No.
哦对了
By the way.
我完全不理解他为什么不留下
I so don't understand why him left in the first place.
基地明显是
I mean the bucker is the.
最安全的地方
Safest place for him.
Bartholomew之流 不知道还有多少天使
Bartholomew and who knows how many other angels.
都在外面等着他
Are out there, gunning for him.
嘿 听着
Hey, look.
没人比我更想让他在这儿了
Nobody wants him here more than I do, okay.
但是
But.
他觉得他会给我们带来麻烦
He felt like he bring trouble down on us.
所以就走了
So he had to split.
如果你有办法 我洗耳恭听
If you get a way to help, I'm all ears.
好吧
All right, so.
Kevin说有工作台在天使坠天那晚
Kevin said the table lit up like.
像圣诞树一般亮了起来 对吧
A Chistmans tree when the angel's fell, right.
- 所以呢 - 所以我发现
- So? - So it turns out.
每个亮点都代表一群天使坠落的地方
Each light was where a cluster of angels fell.
所以我就想 也许有办法能
So I'm thinking, maybe there's some way to hotwire this.
能追查到天使行踪
Maybe can track angels.
这样就能帮Cass了
That way we can help Cass to clear danger.
这是你想出来的
This was…your idea.
你看到这里有其他人吗
Do you see anybody else in here.
怎么做
So how would it work.
还没想好
I have no idea.
开始我觉得那堆工作台都是电脑
See at the first I thought this table was a computer.
后面发现不是 这只是一部分
But it's not.It turns out just a part of it.
但是我在下面发现了这样
But I did find these cables underneath.
然后我跟过去
And I followed them.
你肯定不相信我发现了什么
You're never gonna believe what I've found.
就是这里
Voila.
- 这是电脑吗 - 是的
- This is a computer? - Yeah.
是1951年时装上去的
It was in 1951 when it was installed.
现在这部分
Now.
才是诡异
Here's the crazy thing.
它完全不用插电
It's not plugged in anything.
我完全不知道它是如何工作的
I have no idea what's making these thing work.
这里是热的
It's warm here.
就是这了
Got it.
看起来真简单
Well that looks simple.
有说明书吗
Does it come with a manual.
档案里没有记录
Nothing on the archieves.
在网上也找不到
And obviously couldn't find anything like it online.
而且 我十分确定
Not to mention I'm pretty sure.
那时候学者基地没有
That the men of letters doesn't exactly have.
计算机支持
IT support anymore, either.
我们认识的人里 有人能帮忙吗
Think if you know someboday can help us.
来看看吧
Come on.
有什么想说的吗
So, what do you have to say for yourself.
没有 我把她舌头割掉了
Nothing, I cut out her tongue.
我把她束缚住了 但不会坚持很久
I've bound her, but it won't last.
等等 你抓住了她
Wait, you captured her.
一个人
All by your self.
没错 尽管我是个女人
Yes, despite all my lady parts.
但我还是自己抓住了西方坏女巫
I managed to capture the wicked witch.
你父亲会很骄傲的
Your father would be very proud.
- 你知道他 - 他总是在跟我讲废话
- Did you know - Waste my time with his word.
你要是不像他那样的话 我会很高兴的
I'd appreciate it if you didn't do the same.
现在说正事儿 我试过砍她的头
Now I have tried cutting off her head.
放火烧她 用圣水浇她
Burning her, dousing her with holy water.
她唯一的反应就是大笑
All she did was laugh.
我知道的方法都杀不死她
Nothing I know of can kill her.
所以 我找到你们 做最后一搏
So, I'm here as a last resort.
我希望你们有方法
I was hoping you stiffs have.
杀死从绿野仙踪里来的生物
A way to kill someone from Oz.
我们当然有方法
Of course we do.
我是说 我们必须有
We have to.
这里是最后的灯塔
This place is the last true beacon of light.
别废话了 赶紧去啃你们那堆破书吧
All right, just open your damn book already.
好吧 Jenkins
Alright, Jenkins.
咱们开工了
Let's go to work.
就是这儿了
Here it is.
嘿
Hey.
谢谢你能过来
Thanks for coming.
小事一桩
Not a problem.
尤其是正赶上我刚被炒鱿鱼的时候
Especially since I got fired last week.
怎么回事儿
What?What happened.
我工作的那家公司
Turns out the company I work for.
在向外承包童工
Was outsourcing to child labour.
所以
So.
我就把这件事情抖了出去
I took a big wikileak all over that.
后果可想而知
And yeah.
不过这样也挺好
It's cool, though.
让我有时间发展个人爱好
Give me more time for my hobby.
比如
Like.
真人游戏RPG 编编花边儿
Larping, macrame.
还有猎魔什么的
And hunting.
你什么
Excuse me.
只是几个小案子
Okay, it's just a couple of little cases.
我干掉了一只小吸血鬼和一只鬼魂
I took down a teenage vampire and a ghost.
听起来可能有点儿像少年文学小说
Which sounds like a Y.A. novel if you say it out loud.
Charlie
Charlie.
你完成的顺利吗
How did it go.
这个嘛
It was.
有点儿困难
It was intense.
我以前一直觉得
I kind of wish.
猎魔应该是
Hunting was more.
更奇幻一点儿的
Magical, you know.
当我没说
Never mind.
那么 你们那台克门多尔64在哪儿
So, where is this Commodore 64 of yours.
伟大的Ada Lovelace啊
Sweet Ada Lovelace.
这东西应该放进博物馆里
This thing belongs in a museum.
它居然有一个解码软件
I mean, it's got encryption software.
而且看上去它的能源来自某种奇妙的魔法
It seems to be powered by something magical.
直接说结果
Skip to the end.
这是一种报警机制
It's kind of an alarm system.
全球毁灭性灾难 是很瘆人
Global badness?It freaks.
但是这台电脑会锁住这个地方
This computer is what locked this place down.
我们能用它追踪天使吗
Can we use it to track angels.
好吧
All right.
我会尽我所能
Let me see what I can do.
好了
All right.
虽然花费了点儿时间 但是现在都搞定了
It took some doing but now we can download.
这台怪兽保存着学者们所有的资料
This beast has all the Men of Letters files.
是时候挪挪咱们的鼠标了
Time for a little drag-and-drop.
这是个好的开始
Well, it's a start.
谢谢了
Thank you.
你太厉害了
That's great.
所以你一直在猎魔
So you've been hunting.
一个人
Alone.
我知道
I know.
一个人猎魔违反了邪恶力量小说里的猎人守则
Not a good idea according to the Supernatural books.
你真的不能帮我们把那些书从网上删掉吗
You really can't delete those from the Internet.
没有人能做到完全删除
Not even I can do that.
别这么小气嘛
But come on.
你究竟是在什么地方找到这些书的
Where do you even find them.
一个秘密基地 我管它叫亚马逊购物商城
The top secret place I call Amazon.
有人把未出版部分也发到网上了
And someone uploaded all the unpublished works.
开始我还以为是同人小说
I thought it was fanfic at first.
后来发现真的是Edlund的原著
But it was clearly Edlund's work.
到底是谁上传的
Who uploaded it.
不知道
I don't know.
那人的网名
Their screen name was.
是Beckywinchester176
Beckywinchester176.
想起什么人吗
Ring a bell.
没有 完全没有
None, nobody's.
一点儿想法都没有
No, there're no bells.
没有
No.
这些文件都加密了
These files are encrypted.
要全解开得花点儿时间
This is gonna take a while.
那么接下来 叫点儿外卖
So, takeout.
一起熬个夜 互相编个辫子
Sleepover, braid each other's hair.
我有个主意
Got an idea.
那个小国王Joffery真不是个东西
Wow that Joffery's a dick.
你完全想不到
You've no idea.
直到他
Wait, until he.
别剧透
Spoilers.
书我还没看完呢
I haven't read all the books yet.
你放着电视不看 去看书吗
You're gonna read the books.
没错 Dean 我就是喜欢看书
Yes, Dean, I like to read books.
就是没有图片的一堆字儿 懂吗
You know the ones without pictures.
天 这床跟板儿砖一样硬
Man, this bed is as comfortable as a brick.
打算什么时候搬进来住吗
Any plans on moving in anytime soon.
我已经搬进来了 这就是我的风格
I am moved in, this is just my style.
是啊 他的风格
Yeah, this is his style.
我真抱歉 我还没挂起那张
Well, I'm sorry, I haven't hung up the.
坚持住啊 喵仔 主题的海报 Dean
"Hang in there, kitty"poster yet, Dean.
你随便挂什么都行
Feel free to redecorate.
怎么 咱家配不上你的
So, what, our home's not good enough.
喵仔海报吗
For the "Hang in there, kitty"poster.
这儿不是咱们的家
This isn't our home.
这儿只是咱们工作的地方
This is where we work.
有什么不一样吗
What's the difference.
呃
Okay.
好吧
All right, well.
我去多拿点儿啤酒过来怎么样
I'm gonna go get us some more beers.How about that.
那么 Charlie
So Charlie.
能跟我讲讲你为什么觉得猎魔不神奇了吗
What was al that about how hunting isn't magical.
帮助别人 杀魔除怪 家族事业
Saving people, hunting things, family business.
我表示理解
I'm down.
但是
But.
我是读着Tolkienn奇幻小说长大的
I was raised on Tolkien, man.
小说里写的那些都去哪儿了
I mean, where is all this.
我的异鬼都去哪儿了
Where are my White Walkers.
还有我的火山和魔戒
And my volcano and magic ring to throw in the damn thing.
我的
Where.
我的冒险去哪儿了
Where is my quest.
魔法 冒险
Magic, quests.
都很艰难
Suck.
相信我
Trust me.
他们都是
They're all.
死路一条
Dead ends.
什么办法都没有
Nothing but dead ends.
应该有方法能杀掉这东西啊
There's got to be some way to kill this thing.
Jenkins 不
Jenkins, no.
这儿有一样属于我的东西
There's something here that belongs to me.
把它交还给我
Take me to it.
她到底在说什么
What the hell's it talking about.
我不知道
I have no idea.
你有实验室吗
Do you have a lab.
二楼 28号房
Second floor, room 28.
等等
Wait.
Jenkins Jenkins
Jenkins!Jenkins.
我知道你还在
I know you are in there.
Jenkins早没了
Jenkins is gone.
Jenkins
Jenkins.
你说的对
You're right.
没有比冒险更糟的了
There's nothing worse than adventure.
Dorothy
Dorothy.
Dorothy你在哪儿
下载应该都好了
Dowload should be done by now.
怎么回事
What the hell.
Sam 帮我一下
Sam, give me a hand.
我的个天
Holy crap.
这所学者基地研究的第一个案子
The first case investigated in this bunker.
就跟Dorothy有关
Involved Dorothy.
她带着女巫来到这间屋子
She and the witch came into this room.
但却再也没有出来
And they never came out.
这事儿我永远也忘不掉了
This would never stop blowing my mind.
别激动 托托（绿野仙踪里的宠物狗）
Okay, pace yourself, Toto.
这怎么会是真的 那是童话故事的一部分
How is this real, it's part of the fairy world.
- 你们必须找到她 - 不 在采取任何行动之前
- You have to find her - No we have to talk.
我们需要谈谈
Before anyone does anything, okay.
Dorothy
Dorothy.
谈谈
Talk.
典型的学者口吻
Typical Men of Letters.
假模事事的围过来
Standing around.
文绉绉的谈上半天
Having a nice little chat with your noses.
一边把脸埋进你们的书里
Buried in your books.
一边让你们的小秘书记笔记
While your little secretary takes notes.
我们是猎人
We're hunters.
你管谁叫小秘书呢
And who you're calling a secretary.
你不是秘书吗
So you're not the sacretary.
难道你是女学者
You're a Women of Letters.
我到底被封印了多久
How long have I been out.
所以咱们需要谈谈
That's why we need to talk.
你已经被封印了75年之久了
Look, you've been gone for over 75 years.
根据这些资料来看
According to our files.
你来这儿是为了杀死西方坏女巫
You came here to kill the wicked witch.
但随后就失踪了
And then disappeared.
到底发生了什么
What happened.
我们无法杀死她
We couldn't find a way to kill her.
所以我就做了我能做的
So I did the only thing that I could.
咱俩得耗上一辈子了 贱人
It's you and me forever, bitch.
Dorothy
Dorothy.
一个束缚咒
A binding spell.
但是有代价
That came at a price.
我和她灵魂束缚在一起
Her soul with mine.
所以这些年来 你都和那个女巫困在一起
So you've been frozen with a witch for all this time.
是的
Yes.
听着
Look.
女巫是杀不死的
The witch cannot be killed.
如果我逃脱了咒语 那她也一样
If I'm away and so is she.
你好呀 亲爱的
Hello, lovely.
真抱歉
Sorry.
这条线被下了防魔咒语
This little box is worded against everything.
西方坏女巫也不例外
Even wicked witches.
我可是您的大粉丝
Big fan.
特别喜欢您的创意
Love your work.
怎么了 亲爱的
What's the matter, darling.
胆小的狮子把你的舌头咬掉了吗
Cowardly Lion got your tongue.
好吧
Right.
谈心谈够了
Enough chitchat.
你来这儿肯定是有原因的
You must be here for a reason.
写下来
Write it down.
我就能帮你了
So daddy can help.
等等 如果她在这儿
Wait if she's here.
她为什么不杀了你
Why didn't she kill you.
她杀不了我
She can't.
她被北方好女巫的吻保护了
She's protected by the Witch of the North's kiss.
书里写的
It's from the books.
忘了那些破书吧
Forget the books.
完全不值一提
They're not important.
我被保护了
I'm protected.
但你们没有
You aren't.
女巫到这儿来
Now the witch came here.
她在找什么东西 我完全没有头绪
Looking for something I have no idea what it is.
所以咱们必须在她得逞之前找到她
So we have to find her before she finds it.
好吧
All right.All right.
Charlie你去那些资料里找找看
Charlie dig into the files see if you could find anything.
有没有什么方法能杀死女巫
That puts a dent in a witch.
Sam和我去四处查看一下 来吧
Sam and I will look and see, come on.
我也能帮忙
I'm helping.
我不怀疑这一点
I don't doubt it.
但是现在 你还是留下歇一歇
But for right now, why don't you rest up.
顺便帮帮屋子里最聪明的那个人吧
And help the smartest person in the room.
那么
So.
我可是大粉丝
Big fan.
- 大魔法师奥兹人怎么样 - 是个大混蛋
- How's the Wizard of Oz - It's a total ass.
你在书里要温和多了
You were much nicer in the book.
那些书就是个悲哀老头的胡言乱语
Those books are the ravings of a sad old man.
我父亲的胡言乱语
My father.
等等
Wait.
你爸爸是L Frank Baum吗 书的作者
Your dad was L.Frank Baum, the writer.
同时还是个学者
A Men of Letters.
又是另一个光荣的图书馆管理员 你说呢
Another glorified libarian, you ask me.
喂
Hey.
这些家伙可能有些性别歧视
These guysmay have been sexist.
但是他们都非常聪明
But like all libarians, they're wicked smart, too.
你第一次来的时候看见的那个男人 Haggerty
The dude who was here when you came in, Haggerty.
他一直留着你的资料
He kept your case filed opened.
直到退休之前 都在研究那个案子
Worked it everyday until he retired.
显然 他没能找到你
Obviously he'd never found you.
但如果你花点时间读一读这些资料
But if you took five seconds to read.
就会发现他找到了打败西方坏女巫的办法
He did find a way to fight the wicked witch.
你还记得第一部里面的罂粟花田吗
Do you remember the Poppy fields in the first book.
事实跟书里写的大相径庭
That's actually not how it happened.
更血腥一点
It was much bloodier.
请别再毁我童年了好吗
Stop ruining my childhood.
你还记得那些罂粟吗
Do you remember the poppies.
很好
Good.
Haggerty和一个仙子做了交易
Haggerty made a deal with a fairy.
得到了一些罂粟花提取物
And got some poppy extract.
我要用几把枪做点儿小改动
I'm gonna get some bullet from the gun range.
做一些罂粟子弹
And make some poppy bullets.
那么
So.
你要不要一起来
Are you coming or what.
来的可不是稻草人和铁皮人吗
If it isn't the Scarecrow and the Tin Man.
你们那位新来的客人
Your new house guest.
真是被误解了
So misunderstood.
你们看见她干坏事了吗
Neither of you saw wicked.
她对你说了什么
What did she say to you.
比如
Something along the lines of.
我要去拿点圣油和打火机
All right, I'm gonna get some holy oil and a lighter.
老混蛋
Dick bag.
我知道她在找什么
I know what she's looking for.
她在找什么
What does she want.
我很乐意告诉你们
I'd be happy to tell you.
不过我更愿意活动活动我的腿
As soon as I get to stretch my legs.
很好
All right.
那个女巫到底想要什么
What does the witch want.
再等等
Give me a mo.
我还没遛跶够呢
I still need to air myself out.
我觉得你已经活动够了
I think you've aired out enough.
真粗鲁
Rude.
钥匙
Key.
什么钥匙
What key.
我也不清楚
I haven't the foggiest.
必须在她杀了我之前
Had to send her off a merry chase.
把她支开
Before she could melt me.
我告诉她 你们把钥匙藏在了厨房里
Told her you boys kept the keys in the kitchen.
你们的确有间厨房 对吧
You do have a kitchen in this crap, don't you.
混蛋 我才刚打扫过这儿
Damn it I just cleaned it here.
真的吗
Really.
所以女巫来过这儿
Looks like we got a witch here.
抱歉 我们改装了你们的枪
Sorry we raided your gun range.
做了一些罂粟子弹
Made us some poppy bullets.
不足以杀死女巫
They won't kill the witch.
但是够她好受的了
But they will stun the crap out of her.
这才是我的好女孩儿
That's my girl.
材料只够做四枚子弹 所以
There's only enough for four bullets, so.
射得准点儿
Make each shot count.
现在咱们只需要赶紧找到她
Now we'll just have to find her.
在她找到她想要的东西之前
Before she finds whatever the hell she's looking for.
她在找一把钥匙
She's looking for a key.
你们怎么知道
How do you know.
小鸟传的话
Little birdie told us.
有没有想起什么线索
Ring any bells Dorothy.
真不幸
Unfortunately.
那是通往奥兹的钥匙
It's the key to Oz.
有很多方法可以通往奥兹
There're magical ways into Oz.
龙卷风 台风眼 或者大漩涡
Tornado, eye of a hurricane, whirlpool.
但是这把钥匙能让所有大门
But this key will turn any locked door.
统统大开
Into a portal to Oz.
插入钥匙 转动 只需一眨眼的功夫
Insert key, twisted, and presto.
你就能到达奥兹
You and Oz.
学者是怎么拿到那把钥匙的
How did the Men of Letters get the key.
我也不知道
I have no idea.
但如果她找到了钥匙
But if she finds it.
她肯定会回到奥兹 完成她的阴谋
She'll go back and finish what she started.
她会毁了奥兹
She'll destroy all that is good in Oz.
她有女巫军团
She's got armies of witches.
会飞的猴子
Flying monkeys.
会有很多人因此死去
Many will die.
钥匙长什么样子
What is this key look like.
我见过这把钥匙
I've seen that key.
我在整理目录的时候看到的
Found it when I was doing inventory.
它现在在哪儿
Where is it now.
我的卧室里
My room.
我们要马上去找到那把钥匙
We got to get to that key.
Charlie和我去我的卧室
Alright, Charlie and I will go look into my room.
你们俩给我们争取点儿时间
Why don't you guys buy us some time.
Charlie
Charlie.
这儿最安全的地方 是一个地牢
Safest place in this joint, is a dungeon.
你们居然还有地牢
You have a dungeon in this place.
当然 你们当然有
Of course you do.
所以你也许应该
So maybe you should.
我才不要藏起来
I'm not hiding.
尤其是藏在地牢里
Especially in a dungeon.
西方坏女巫 神秘的钥匙 一个大冒险
Wicked witch, a key, a quest.
我一定不能错过
I'll do this.
Charlie
Char-Charlie.
真不敢相信我在这儿待了75年
I can't believe I've lived here for 75 years.
你们管这地方叫家有多长时间了
How long have you called this place home.
我哥把这儿当家
My brother calls it home.
但是我 家对我来说可不是什么好主意
Me, I…don't have that much luck with homes.
跟我一样
Me neither.
家总是没有想象中那么好
Overrated, if you asked me.
那条金砖小路给了我逃离家的机会
Yellow bricks or not gives me the open road any day.
Sam
Sam.
她从那里面能去任何地方
She can get any where from there.
分头行动 更快
Slip up, cover more ground.
你居然把色情小说整理得那么整齐
You keep your porn meticulously organized, but not.
别评论我
Don't judge me.
找到了
Yahtzee.
Dean
Dean.
Charlie
Charlie.
不
No.
Dean
Dean.
Zeke
Zeke.
你得帮帮她
You got to help her.
她已经去了
She's gone.
不 但你可以救她
No, you can bring her back.
就像你救Cass那样
Like what you did with Cass.
我不能经常这么做
I can't keep doing that.
为什么不行
Why the hell not.
我的力量还没有恢复到一半 Dean
I'm barely back to half strength, Dean.
每次我使用能力
Every time I use my power.
都会使我更虚弱
It weakens me.
这就意味着我需要在你弟弟身体里
Which means I have to stay in your brother.
待更久的时间
Longer than you want.
这是你我都不愿看到的
Longer than we both want.
那个女巫
The witch.
那个在基地里的女巫力量非常强大
Running around your bunker is very powerful.
我可以帮你们杀死女巫
I can help with the witch.
或者救你的朋友
Or save your friend.
救她
Save her.
如你所愿
As you wish.
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.
Charlie
Charlie.
我认识你
I know you.
我不是告诉你要藏在地牢里
I told you to stay in the dungeon.
我猜你对所有姑娘都这么说
Bet you say that to all the girls.
Dean
Dean.
Sammy
Sammy.
刚才发生了什么
What the hell just happened.
女巫
The witch.
女巫出现了 要对我施咒
The witch was about to put a whammy on me.
但是Charlie跳起来保护了我
And Charlie jumped in front.
她就中招了 然后女巫把你也放倒了
She got zapped, then the witch got the drop on you.
那我们怎么没死
Then why aren't we dead.
问的好
That's a good question.
我
I.
我用罂粟子弹吓跑了她
I clipped her with a with a poppy bullet.
但她拿走了钥匙
She got the key.
我觉得她已经走了
I think she's gone.
不 她受伤了
No, she's wounded.
我们还有时间
We should still have some time.
她可能还藏在排气管道里
She could still be in the air vents.
不不不 她说的对
No, no, no, she's right.
我们必须
We, we have to.
你们先走
Just go.
我们随后就到
We'll catch up.
我的枪在那儿
My gun's over there.
就剩一颗子弹了
There's one bullet in it.
咱们现在能做好朋友了吗
Can we be best friends now.
Zeke是谁
Who's Zeke.
什么
What.
我跑进你房间的时候
When I came into your room.
在我被放倒之前
Before I got zapped.
我好像听见你叫了Zeke
I thought you said the name Zeke.
那是谁
Who's that.
你现在是不是还没清醒过来呢 伙计
I think you're still a little punchy, man.
先走着再说
Just keep moving.
我做了一个奇怪的梦
I had the weirdest dream when I was out.
正好是圣诞节 我的父母还都活着
It was Christmas, and my parents were still alive and.
梦
Dream.
Charlie 你死了
Charlie, you dies.
但是 别担心
Don't worry about it, though.
没有经历过死亡
You're not a real hunter.
就不能算是个好猎人
Until you've died and come back again.
等等
Slow down.
你为什么说我死了
Why would you think I die.
天堂
Heaven.
那里有你梦想的生活
It's your dream life.
而且如果你被西方坏女巫的魔咒击中
And if you were zapped by the wicked witch.
几乎是即刻死亡
Instant death.
我知道 因为她也杀死过我
I would know.She killed me, too.
好吧
Okay.
咱们往前倒一倒
Let's rewind here a bit.
你什么时候死的
When did you die.
在奥兹的时候
In Oz.
我父亲对学者的工作嫉妒痴迷
My father was obsessed with his work as a Man of Letters.
随后我诞生了
And then I was born.
但这并不能改变什么
And nothing changed.
他对自己的工作闭口不谈
He would keep his work a secret.
但我是个好奇心很重的孩子
But I was such a curious kid.
总能卷进各种各样的麻烦
I was always looking for trouble.
寻找着一个又一个冒险
Looking for the next big adventure.
我知道这种感觉
I know the feeling.
我悄悄尾随他去了翡翠城
I stowed away on one of his cases.
结果在那儿受了伤
Wound up in the emerald city.
偶然的被落在了那儿
Accidentally got left behind.
当时我真被吓坏了
It was terrifying.
发生了什么
Well, what happened.
我遇到了三个自由的斗士
I met up with these three freedom fighters.
他们认为我就是那个命中注定
And they thought I was this child of destiny.
杀死西方坏女巫的孩子
Chosen to kill the wicked witch.
所以他们保护了我 然后
They protected me, and then.
女巫把他们变成了
The witch turned them into.
稻草人 铁皮人和一只狮子
A scarecrow, a tin man and a lion.
然后她就开始猎杀我
And then she hunted me down.
她杀了我
And killed me.
但书里可没有把这一段也写上
Yeah, that never made it to the books.
有时候 现实生活比小说里更加不堪
Sometimes real life is darker than fiction.
你为什么不搬进来住
Why haven't you moved in.
现在真是谈这个的好时机吗 Dean
Is now really the time for this, Dean.
就是问问
Well, just asking.
我不像你一样有跟爸妈在一起的美好记忆 好吗
Look, I never had what you had with mom and dad, okay.
你在说什么
What are you talking about.
我没有对家的回忆
I don't have any memories of home.
而且每次我试图组建一个家庭的时候
And whenever I've tried to make a home of my own.
坏事儿就会发生
It really hasn't ended well.
是啊 但是住了一辈子破房子
Yeah, but a lifetime of abandoned buildings.
和恶心的汽车旅店
And crappy motel rooms, I mean.
这儿就是咱们能有的最像家的地方了
This is about as close to home as we're gonna get.
而且这儿是咱们的
And it's ours.
那些书又是怎么回事儿
And what about the books.
那只是被篡改了的历史
Revisionist history.
那是我父亲想要记录我的经历的
That's my father's way of trying to undo.
一种方式
What had happened to me.
但是我知道真相
But I knew the truth.
当女巫来到我的世界时
When the witch came to our world.
我成为了一个猎人
I became a hunter.
但我父亲却写了那些愚蠢的书
And my father wrote those silly books.
你还不明白吗
Don't you get it.
那些书并不愚蠢
The books aren't silly.
他们是你父亲留给你的线索
They're guidebooks filled with clues he left for you.
学者Haggerty仔细研读了每一本
Haggerty pored through each one.
他的研究让他找到了罂粟的秘密
And his research led him to uncover the poppies.
所以或许书里还有什么
So maybe there's something else.
是我们可以用到的
From the books we can use.
希望可以找到结束女巫的方法
Preferably something with a pointy end.
你确实是个天才
You are a genius.
来吧 咱们去车库
Come on, we've got to get to the garage.
这儿还有个车库
There's a garage in this place.
天呐 男孩子们
Oh, boy.
这边一切正常
Clear.
我什么也没看到
I got nothing.
你怎么想
What do you think.
她走了吗
Is she gone.
Sam
Sam.
找到女孩们
Find the girls.
把她们全杀了
And kill them all.
太好了 我知道那些童子军会帮我留着它的
Yes, I know the boys scouts were gonna keep it for me.
那是
Is that.
是的 他没能挺过来
Yeah, he didn't make it.
一定要在这儿啊
Please be here.
太好了
Yes.
真是难以置信
I don't believe it.
你真的穿着这个走过那条金砖小路吗
Did you really walk down a brick road in these.
不其实我从来没穿过它们
No, I never actually wore them.
穿一个死人的鞋感觉可不怎么好
Seemed kind of tacky wearing a dead woman's shoes.
而且 我穿高跟鞋不好看 你懂的
Plus, I'm no good in heels, you know.
咱们大概不能直接用祈祷的方式赶走她对吧
I don't suppose we could just wish her away.
抱歉 另一件书里说错的事
Sorry, another thing that the book got wrong.
但是 就像罂粟花一样
But, like the poppies.
它们具有奥兹的魔力
These are magic from Oz.
强大的魔力
Sharp magic.
用鞋子杀死女巫吗
Death by shoe.
你们在这儿
There you are.
那是你们的蝙蝠侠嗓音吗
Is that your Batman voice.
那肯定不是你们的蝙蝠侠嗓音
That's definitely not your Batman voice.
是她
It's her.
她把他们都附身了
She possessed the both of them.
我想你了 小美人
I miss you, my pretty.
第二次杀你
Killing you a second time.
会像第一次一样甜蜜
Will be just as sweet as the first.
你们两个 我知道你们还在
Guys, I know you are in there.
Dean 你不能让女巫得逞
Dean, you can't let the witch do this.
如果她把那个门打开了
If she opens the door.
她会毁掉我们
She's going to destroy us.
我根本没想着要逃去奥兹
I have no intention of escaping to Oz.
我要把我的军队带到这里
I'm going to bring my armies here.
别担心 你会在死后与Dorothy相见的
Don't worry, you'll join the Dorothy after you die.
真抱歉 这可能会很痛 Dean
Sorry about the nerves Dean.
快走 我会给你争取点时间
Go, I'll buy you some time.
好吧 让我看看你们的嫩脖子有多结实
All right, let's see what you pencil necks are made of.
好吧 我们用古老的方法来
All right, let's do this the old fashion way.
我的身体伤害不了你 Dorothy
My body cannot hurt you, Dorothy.
但是他们的可以
But theirs can.
现在 上鞋跟
Now heel.
刚才发生了什么
What the hell just happened.
Charlie
Charlie.
叮咚 小贱人们
Ding dong, Bitches.
真的要这样吗 在我做完一切之后
Really, after what I did with Ms.defying gravity.
混蛋
Bollocks.
我的黑美人在这儿看起来不错嘛
Baby looks good in here.
确实
Not bad.
Dean
Dean.
Dorothy 我在档案馆找到了点东西
Dorothy, I found something in the archives.
我确定这属于你
I'm sure it belongs to you.
你不知道那有多奇怪
You have no idea how odd it is.
有一系列的书在写你
Having a series of books writing about you.
其实 我知道
Actually, I do know.
那的确很奇怪
And it is definitely weird.
你知道吗
You know what.
说到底
In the end of the day.
这是我们的故事
It's our story.
所以我们书写
So we get to write it.
那么 谢谢你们的闺蜜之夜
So, thanks for the slumber party.
还有 让我死而复生
And bringing me back from the dead.
我没有
I didn't.
别跟流氓耍流氓
Don't BS a BS-er.
我现在是僵尸吗
Am I a zombie now.
我需要吃大脑吗
Do I need to eat brains.
不 不 你是你
No, no, you are you.
你会没事的
You are gonna be fine.
好吗 就
All right, just.
这事儿替我保密 好吗
Just keep this between us, okay.
好吧
Alright.
只是因为你把我救活了
But only base on you bringing me back from dead.
那是你待会一定要跟我解释的
Which you are going to explain to me later.
好吧
Alright.
对一群图书管理员来说 你们还不错
Not bad for a bunch of librarian.
介意帮我照看一下我的车吗
Mind keep an eye on my bike for me.
好的 好的 只要你不介意
Yeah, Yeah, as long as you don't mind me.
我时不时开着它出去遛遛
Taking it for a spin once in a while.
成交
Deal.
谢谢你们 为所有的事情
Thank you, for everything.
现在 请原谅我
Now if you excuse me.
我还有个叛乱要去处理
I have a rebellion to finish.
你要跟我一起来吗
So, you are coming or what.
什么 和你 去奥兹
What, with you to Oz.
是啊 你说你在寻找冒险
Yeah, you said you are looking for adventure.
这就是了 不是吗
Well, here it is, right.
来帮我找到那该死的狗
Come Help me to find the damn dog.
你不知道奥兹里有什么
You have no idea what's in the Oz.
我是说那里有会飞的猴子 女巫军团
I mean there are flying monkeys, armies of witches.
各种危险
All kinds of danger.
你保证
Promise.
如果你们需要什么
If you need anything.
就敲鞋跟三下 好吗
Just tap your heels together three times, okay.
我吗
Me.
你们两个疯娃子呢
What about you crazy kids.
你们没有我会好好的吧
You are gonna be all right without me.
你们自己保重 男孩们
Take care of yourself, boys.
你觉得她会回来吗
Think she'll be back.
当然 哪也没有家里好
Of course, there's no place like home.